PROFILE

Software engineer with front-end tendencies who has five years industry experience in mobile/web application development, large scale projects built with the Microsoft .NET frameworks, and automated testing/deployment. Looking for a position to work on projects currently leveraging the latest web technologies.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF NEVADA RENO, Reno, NV

December 2013

Master of Business Administration – GPA: 3.88

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA LOS ANGELES, Los Angeles, CA

June 2010

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science – GPA: 3.00

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

SINPAL, Las Vegas, NV

May 2015 - November 2015

Startup Idea – Technical Co-founder

- Assumed project level ownership of designing and implementing an event-based nightlife app
- Front-end: HTML5/CSS/Javascript/Bootstrap/Handlebars
- Back-end: NodeJS/Redis/RabbitMQ in the Heroku ecosystem
- Reached Round 2 of idea applications for The Mill Accelerator Program
- Website: www.sinpal.com

INTERNATIONAL GAME TECHNOLOGY, Reno, NV

June 2010 - May 2014

Systems R&D – Software Engineer II

- iOS developer on a Dutch-style auction based mobile app which uses casino loyalty comps as currency.
- Knowledgeable in client-server technologies such as cloud web services, REST API calls and JSON/XML.
- Set up continuous integration testing tools such as Jenkins and Testflight for nightly ad-hoc builds
- Integrated functional testing tools such as MonkeyTalk for automated testing of builds
- 3 years experiences working on casino in-house desktop applications built using C#/WPF/WCF in the .NET framework as a member of the User Interface team in the Systems R&D department.
- Experience in project methodologies such as the waterfall model, agile scrum, and pair programming.
- Certified Scrum Master (January 24, 2014 Scrum Alliance Inc.)

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

GAP YEAR May 2014 – May 2015

- Gained a fresh perspective on the world after traveling through 29 countries over the span of six months
- Adapted to many different cultures and languages while sharpening my negotiation and interpersonal skills
- Developed better understanding of construction, planning, and budgeting working with my father on a threemonth renovation project that overhauled a 3000 square feet commercial unit into a banquet room

Recreational Activities

- Hiking, Snowboarding, Skiing, Indoor Rock Climbing, Football, Basketball,
- Scuba Diving (PADI Certified: Open Water Diver)